Contact

parrid70@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/denise-parrish-96561065 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing ACLS Inpatient

Denise Parrish

Vice President of Clinical Operations & CNO Sandusky, Ohio

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Physician Relations, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Team Building, and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Education from University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh.

Experience

Firelands Regional Medical Center Vice President of clinical operations & CNO July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) Sandusky, Ohio

Affinity Health System 22 years 1 month

RN

July 1997 - July 2019 (22 years 1 month)

Nurse Manager June 2011 - February 2014 (2 years 9 months)

Ascension
Chief Administrative Officer (CAO)
July 1997 - July 2019 (22 years 1 month)
Oshkosh, Wisconsin Area

University of Wisconsin Oshkosh Instructional Academic Staff August 2009 - June 2011 (1 year 11 months)

US Army
Operating Room Technician
June 1990 - June 1994 (4 years 1 month)

Education

University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh

Master's degree, Nursing Education · (2006 - 2009)

University of Wisconsin-Oshkosh
Bachelor's of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1994 - 1997)